Inaudit is a performative investigation
into sound and the body,
exploring unheard and inaudible sonic
memory
in buildings, landscapes, streets, houses:
places with a heritage of their own,
an intimate world of sound we cannot hear,
which we investigate and discover through
this piece,
sharing experiences with the audience that
change
with each different performance we create.
A space filled with distinctive sounds
and a historical weight that has fallen on
our shoulders
and has been difficult to deal with.
We have treated the memory of this place
with great respect,
because anything we might say,
anything we might do or wear,
anything that happens in this space
carries so many meanings,
and the way it affected us was quite
paralysing.
Creació i Museus is sonic heritage.
Creació i Museus means going beyond the
layers.